麦克斯 小心 你都累得
Max, look out, you're so tired
把面粉糊洒自己身上了
you're spilling batter all over yourself.
我就知道这天迟早会来
I knew it was only a matter of time
我成了洒面糊的笨女人
before I became a battered woman.
这真是太让人失望了
This is a huge disappointment.
我听见咯
I heard that.
你又不知道我是指什么
You don't even know what I'm referring to.
我就当你是指这一切好啦
Oh, I just assumed we were talking about everything.
我是在说我们所费不赀的小蛋糕网站
I'm referring to our expensive new cupcake website.
一笔找上门的生意都没有
Not one job offer.
想看个能让你心情爽一点的网站吗
You want a website that will make you feel better about yourself?
去模特跌倒网看看吧
Go to models-falling-down.Com
最好笑的是"名模克劳姆狗吃屎"
Number one: Klum goes boom.
半夜三点 谁会这个时候来敲门呀
It's 3 A.M. Who would be coming over now?
不知道 我的药头吧 或药头二号
I don't know, my dealer, my other dealer?
或老问我 我药头上哪去的那个男的
That guy who always asks if I know where my dealer is?
谁啊
Who is it?
门外的东西 你承受不起
You can't handle what's on the other side of that door.
昨天 我看见一个男人在阳台上
Yesterday, I saw a guy on a stoop
跟他的猫舌吻
frenching his cat.
我还有什么承受不了的啊
I can handle anything.
奥列格 你这么晚来干嘛
Oleg, what are you doing here?
和服都让你穿成"合吐"了
And you put the, "oh, no," in kimono.
你们楼上的邻居 苏菲
Your upstairs neighbor Sophie
恩准我跟她上床
is allowing me to have sex with her.
我下来借点按摩油
And I came down to borrow some sensual oils.
可外用内服的为佳
Preferably, ones that you can eat.
你怎么出来了
How did you get out of apartment?
不是跟你说过规矩吗
You know the rules.
我下来借按摩油嘛
I came down to borrow sensual oils.
对哦 不能别含有薄荷成分哦
Yeah, but no peppermint.
不然他的舌头会肿
It makes his tongue swell.
不怕直说
And let's face it,
他全身上下最管用的 就是那条舌头了
his tongue is the best part about him.
你说得对 我的确承受不住
You're right, I can't handle that.
2号卡座那两位香喷喷的男士
Those nice smelling men in booth two
问我是不是"密柜中人"
just asked me if I was on the down-low.
那是什么意思啊
What does this mean?
兄弟
Uh, brother,
得有上下文才能解读啊
I'm gonna need a little more context.
他们问 "你是不是密柜中人啊
They said, "are you on the down-low,
我们有个朋友是超米后哟"
because we have a friend who is a big-time rice queen."
还是理解不能
Again, coming up dry.
米后 是跟韩国的奶品皇后差不多咩
Rice queen, is it, like, a Korean dairy queen?
差不多吧
Kind of.
7号桌结账 厄尔
Here's table seven's check, Earl.
麦克斯 2号卡座的两个男的
Max, the guys at booth two
刚问阿憨是不是密柜中人
just asked Han if was on the down-low.
他们以为他是小基佬呢
They think he's gay.
不错啊 比以前好了
That's a step up.
一般人家都以为他是拉拉
Usually people think he's a lesbian.
给 苏菲
Here you go, Sophie.
麦克斯 卡洛琳
Uh, Max, Caroline.
昨晚的事情...
Yeah, about last night,
我希望你们能保守秘密
I hope we can keep that just between us girls.
大家都有过夜半时分
I'm sure we have all done things in the dark
跟男人背地里"干"一些羞于启齿的事情
late at night with men that we'd like to forget.
干嘛说得只有在夜半时分才干
Why stop at late at night in the dark?
大清早就没做过吗
How about early morning?
大中午在港务局的巴士站干的就不算吗
Or a nooner at the port authority bus terminal?
你理解就好
Oh, good.
你也能理解吗 卡洛琳
And you too understand, Caroline?
老实说 不理解 抱歉
Actually, no, sorry.
我还没跟男人干过任何让我
I haven't ever done anything with a man
-羞于启齿的事 -是吗
- that I'm ashamed of. - Oh, yeah.
你老爸不也骗过人家好几百亿嘛
But your father did steal millions and millions of dollars.
别忘了这档事哟
So... don't forget that.
阿憨刚才服侍了你最爱的基佬们哦
Han just sat your favorite gays.
麦克斯 人家是叫史蒂芬跟迈克
Max, their names are Steven and Michael.
自动就把人归类成基佬 政治立场不太正确吧
And it's not very P.C. to reduce people to a stereotype.
-姑娘们好啊 -还好吗 小可爱们
- Hey, girl. - What's up, care bear?
是啊 他们真不是典型的基佬
Yeah, they're not stereotypes.
要是人家称你为
What would you say if they called you
"那个生于贫民窟 睡遍全高中的巨乳服务生"
"The big-boob waitress from the wrong side of the tracks
你又会作何感想
who had sex with everyone in high school"?
我会说 "就是这样我才爱基佬
I'd say, "that's why I love the gays.
他们真懂我"
They get me."
过去打个招呼吧
Come over and say hello.
人家可是我们的第一批顾客
They're the first and practically the only people
也是唯一请我们做小蛋糕的人
that ever hired us to do a cupcake job.
不去不行吗
Do I have to?
我不能就远远站着 对他们品头论足吗
Can't I just stand here and judge from afar?
来嘛 千万别说咱们生意不好
Come on, and let's not mention how bad we're doing.
要让他们觉得我们大获成功
We want them to think we're a big success,
他们才会放心推荐我们给朋友
so they'll recommend us for their friends' events.
也对 基佬嘛
Yeah, because you know the gays,
什么破事都能开个派对
they party about everything.
又不是每个基佬都这样
And there's another stereotype.
-你们好吗 -闰年快乐啊
- Hi, guys. - Happy leap year!
对了 我们朋友们现在还对
F.Y.I., people are still talking about
你们做的婚前派对小蛋糕赞不绝口呢
those cupcakes you made for our wedding shower.
-人人夸哟 -生意如何
- Everyone. - How's business?
太好了 超棒的 忙得累死累活
Fabulous, amazing, killing it.
或是搞得我们生不如死 说不准啊
Or it's killing us. We're not quite sure.
我去帮你们两姑娘拿菜单过来
I'll go grab some menus for you girls.
-麦克斯 -抱歉
- Max. - Sorry.
我去帮你们两女士拿菜单过来
I'll go grab some menus for you ladies.
爱死她了 超像玛德琳·斯托在《复仇》里角色
Love her... so Madeleine Stowe in revenge.
真的呢
Oh, she is.
-我不看那个剧 -我们超爱看的
- I don't watch that. - We love it.
讲的是一个年轻的金发妹
It's all about a young blonde woman
要向那些摧毁她家庭的人
who's out to seek revenge on everyone
展开复仇的故事
for destroying her family.
不看是对的 太感同身受了
Yeah, too close to home.
-麦克斯 你猜怎么了 -卡洛琳
- Max, guess what. - Caroline, you're not
批斗会还没开始之前 你不能先告诉我
supposed to tell me I'm on intervention
我要被批斗啊
until the actual intervention.
史蒂夫和迈克要出远门
I just got offered $600 to stay at
他们刚说给我600块 让我去他们家呆两天
Steven and Michael's apartment and watch their dogs
帮看家兼养狗
while they're out of town for two days.
怎么会有人愿意花600块
Why would anyone pay $600
请人帮忙养狗呀
to watch dogs for two days?
因为... 他们希望自家的狗
Well, because, you know, they want a certain
得到悉心的照料...
amount of attention to be paid to the...
不就是基佬们
Just say it, they're gay
都把小狗当成自己的孩子养嘛
and they think their dogs are their children.
麦克斯 别再说这种话了
Max, you have to stop doing this.
他们不基 我就不说
I'll stop when they stop.
我好兴奋啊
This is so exciting.
这就跟在高档酒店带薪度假一样
It'll be like a paid vacation at an amazing hotel.
而且我也想离这地方越远越好
And I need to get as far away from here as possible.
-他们住哪里 -四个街区外
- Oh, where do they live? - Four blocks away.
祝你玩得开心
Well, have a good time.
当你在四个街区外
And while you're four blocks away
爽爽地度假时 我会在家
having your vacation, I'll be home
动手给自己"爽爽"
maybe taking a little masturbacation.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我怎么可能抛下你 自己去
I wouldn't go on vacation without you.
平分看狗的钱 整好够补上
We'll split the dog money to cover the shifts
请假时间的薪水
we take off from the diner.
谢了
Well, thanks,
不过我不是请假去玩的人
but I don't do that thing where you take off work.
"你好 我是麦克斯
"Hi, I'm Max,
我不爱去豪华公寓享乐
I can't go to a fancy apartment and have fun.
我宁愿留在炼钢厂
I'd rather work in a steel mill
边工作边哼歌"
and sing Bruce Springsteen songs."
麦克斯 你上次度假是什么时候
Max, when was the last time you had a vacation?
没休过
Never.
除非算上有一年夏天
Unless you count the summer I hid
我在前门阳台下 躲我老妈新男人那次
under the front porch from my mom's new boyfriend.
我们真得脱离这个环境
We really need to get out of here.
这不只是春假
This is more than just spring break.
而是暂时远离餐馆
It's a break from the diner,
远离小蛋糕事业 远离贫穷
from the cupcake business, from being poor,
远离一切不顺心的人事物
from everything depressing right now.
哪有这么凄惨啊
Things aren't that depressing.
我想大家都有过
Yeah, well, I'm sure we have
在厨房里跟男人干一些...
all done things with men in kitchens that...
羞于启齿的事
we are not proud of.
春假是最美好的时光
Spring break is the greatest time ever.
可以无所顾忌 疯狂喝酒
You just go crazy and do shots
把一切教条置之脑后
and throw all the rules out the window.
我也玩过啊
Oh, I've done that.
不过咱们穷人称那为"周二"
But when you're poor, you just call it Tuesday.
你干嘛那样走路
Why are you walking like that?
这是我的春假步
This is my spring break walk.
我曾从马略卡岛一路
These shoulders have shimmied like this
一路晃到伊比沙岛
all the way from Majorca to Ibiza.
试试嘛 麦克斯 晃一下
Try it, Max. Shake a little.
-晃嘛 -是挺酷的
- Shake. - That's cool.
等我享受了环绕音响再晃也不迟
I'll just wait till I get the DTS later.
钥匙是不是不对啊
Maybe I don't have the right key.
你好啊
Oh, hi.
抱歉 我们貌似是开错门了
Sorry, I think we might be at the wrong door.
你说找错 门都伤心死了
That's a bummer for the door.
我们是在那边 12D
It's over there, 12d.
我们来帮朋友看几天家
We're house-sitting for a few days.
太好了 我叫布兰登
Cool, I'm Brendon.
你好啊 布兰登 我是艾希莉
Hey, Brendon. I'm Ashley.
-这位是... -我是"好惊讶"
- And... - I'm surprised.
也是麦克斯啦
And also Max.
虽然我很想跟你们握手 但我有点臭
I'd shake your hands, but I kind of stink.
我大部分时间都呆在自己的家酿酒厂里
I've been at my microbrewery most of the day,
原谅我满身的酵母味
so I am sorry if I smell like yeast.
有酒味就怪我吧
Hey, that's my apology.
好的 那行
Whoa, all right, cool.
那我们回见吧 会见到吧
Well, I will see you guys around, yeah?
当然 会会的
Yeah, totes.
有什么话想对我说吗 艾希莉
You have something you want to tell me, Ashley?
为安全起见 我旅游时从来不用真名
I never use Caroline Channing on vacation for security reasons.
我有次在墨西哥城差点被人
I was almost abducted at gunpoint
用枪指着 要求赎款呢
for a ransom in Mexico city.
哎哟 还用枪指着呢
Wow, gunpoint.
你那时候也说了"会会的" 才被人用枪指的吗
Were you using the word, "totes" at the time?
能帮忙拿出有警报器密码的纸吗
Can you take out the paper that has the alarm code on it?
这地方也太赞了吧
Wow, this place is amazing.
不给《超基基基杂志》当封面 真是可惜了啊
It's, like, the cover of gay gay gay magazine.
麦克斯 别再把人家
Max, you have to stop reducing them
贬低成基佬中的大路货
to that gay stereotype.
快念警报器密码吧
Now, read me the security code.
是"丽莎"
It's..."Liza."
很多不同类型的人都喜欢丽莎·明尼利啊
A lot of different types of people like Liza Minnelli.
瞧 穿着芭蕾舞短裙的小贵宾狗
Oh, look, it's a poodle in a tutu.
这一点都不"基"情四射 对吧
That's not gay, right?
很多...很多人
Lots of... lots of different
都有穿着芭蕾舞裙的小贵宾狗
types of people have a poodle in a tutu...
名字都取"芭芭拉·史翠珊"
Named Barbra Streisand.
看家指南在这里
Oh, there's the book of instructions.
"嗨 姑娘 嗨 小可爱
"Hey, girl. Hey, care bear.
"好好跟芭芭拉·史翠珊与维诺娜·贾德玩吧"
"Have fun with Barbra Streisand and Wynonna Judd.
"维诺娜有点脾气不好
"Wynonna is a little temperamental
喜欢待在卧室里不出来
and tends to stay in the bedroom.
我们临走前来不及帮她清理肛门腺
We didn't have time to purge her anal gland before left.
清理方法详见第二页"
Instructions on page two."
我开始明白为啥给这么多钱了
I'm starting to understand the $600.
"不用紧张 很简单 我们常弄"
"Don't worry, it's easy. We do it all the time."
难怪维诺娜脾气不好了
No wonder Wynonna's so temperamental.
"冰箱里的东西想吃就吃
"Help yourself to anything in the fridge.
衣橱里有家用式桑拿"
There are portable saunas in the closet."
家用式桑拿
Portable saunas?
爱死了 那是什么东西来着
Love it, what is it?
这也太酷了
This is so cool.
就像置身在海滩上一样热
I'm hot like I'm at the beach,
又不用担心踩到用过的保险套
but I'm not stepping in any used condoms.
是啊 这是挺不错的
Yeah, these are great.
我以前有个朋友坎迪丝
My friend Candice Travelstead
靠这个为毕业舞会瘦身
used one to make weight for prom.
你看完了吗
Are you done with that?
看完了 交换吧
Yeah, switch?
以前春假 我很喜欢
On spring break, I always loved
在海滩上赖一整天
spending the day at the beach.
沐浴着春风 跟闺蜜聊天
Just the chilling and the girl talk.
那你再跟我形容一下
Yeah. Tell me again,
刚才挤肛门腺时发出的声响吧
about the sound the anal gland made when you squeezed it.
求你别问了
Please, stop.
我都说过两次了
I already told you twice.
维诺娜·贾德现在都不愿意看我一眼了
And now, Wynonna Judd won't even look at me.
她律师不在场 哪敢靠近你啊
Well, not without her lawyer in the room.
我饿了 你假期都吃什么的啊
I'm hungry. What do you eat on vacation?
爱吃什么吃什么
Anything we want.
来看看吧
Let's see.
他们的冰箱应该装满了各种意大利面
I bet their refrigerator is stocked with all kinds of pates
起司 和起司脆饼之类的吧
and cheeses and those parm crisp things.
泳衣挺好看的啊
By the way, nice suit.
你看起来像饶舌MV里
You look like someone should be pouring
全身被人淋满酒的浪妹子
a 40 on you in a rap video.
多谢夸奖
Thanks.
里面没吃的
There's nothing.
不是吧 他俩当基怎么当的这么失败
I mean, come on, what kind of gays are they?
只有肛腺 其余免谈
All anal gland and no cheese.
我本来对这里满怀期待
I just expected everything to be better.
冰镇着的香槟
You know, champagne on ice,
上千针的高级床单
thousand thread-count sheets.
他们的毛巾 连浴巾都算不上
I mean, the towels... They're not even bath sheets.
什么 那些毛巾不好吗
Wait, the towels aren't good?
我都偷了两条了
Because I already stole two.
其实还行啦 只是跟我期望的有出入而已
They're fine, they're just not what I was expecting.
你是怎么啦
What's happening over there?
摇摇肩膀 甩掉坏心情嘛
You could use a little shoulders.
你说得对 不抱怨了 好好享受假期
You're right, enough, we're on vacay.
来吧 穿好衣服 我们找地方吃饭去
Come on, let's go get dressed and find someplace to eat.
你疯啦 我才不出来
Are you crazy? I am not leaving this thing.
我这辈子从来没这么舒服过
This is the happiest I've ever been in my life.
好吧 叫外卖 假装是酒店客房服务
Okay, we'll order in, pretend it's room service.
应该有个抽屉是放外卖单的吧
They must have a menu drawer here somewhere.
而且 肯定没有可以
Plus, we'll never find a restaurant
携带家用桑拿入内的餐厅
with a portable sauna section.
"美食频道派对之夜
"Food network party tonight
欢庆食谱出版
to celebrate the release of a cookbook.
提供食物与饮品"
food and drink provided."
免费美食家特选食物与饮品呢
Free foodie food, free foodie drinks?
-太爽了 走吧 -不要 我要待这里面
- Yay, let's go. - No, I like it in here.
太舒服了
It's amazing.
艾希莉想去嘛
Ashley wants to go.
艾希莉真的想去嘛
好吧 我能带着狗一起去吗
Fine, but can I bring the dog?
我一直梦想有天能当那种
I've always wanted to be one of those girls
抱着小狗去公共场合的女人
who brings a tiny dog to a public place
然后藐视众生 对所有人说
and just looks at everyone, like,
"老娘就带小狗来 怎么着"
"Yeah, I have a tiny dog, so what?"
你想当什么人就当什么人
You can be whoever you want to be.
假期中就有这权利
You're on vacation.
我要邀请布兰登一起去
I'm gonna go invite Brendon to come.
平生春假不邂逅 若称放假也枉然
You gotta have a crush on spring break.
我已经坐在我的邂逅对象里了
Well, I'm sitting in my crush.
你不用多加件衣服吗
Hey, shouldn't you put something on?
假期就应该露
Uh, it's spring break.
芭芭拉 快去找人来救我
Barbra, get help.
上啊 芭芭拉·史翠珊 冲啊
Go, Barbra Streisand, go.
瞧这书的书名
Hey, look at the book title,
《306度的天堂:培根》
306 degrees of heaven: Bacon.
天堂"培根" 这双关不错
Heaven bacon. That's good wordplay.
还好吧 人不多
It's okay. Not much of a crowd.
派对又有点小闷
Party's a little disappointing.
吃松露培根吗 芭芭拉·史翠珊
Bacon truffle, Barbra Streisand?
我就喂我的小狗吃松露 怎么着
Yeah, I'm feeding my tiny dog a truffle, so what?
小姐 小姐
Miss, miss.
不好意思 这东西是干嘛用的
Excuse me, what are these things for?
您拿食物的时候 可以把饮品放上面
Oh, it holds your drink while you get food.
-不是吧 -是的
- No! - Yeah.
这东西不错 第一次见到都会挺惊奇的
Yeah, these are great when you see them for the first time.
我第一次见 是在地中海的一艘游艇上
For me, it was on a yacht in the Mediterranean.
你知道这玩意儿还能干嘛吗
You know what else these are good for?
解放的你肩膀 让你尽情摇摆
Frees up your shoulders to shimmy.
你慢慢摇 我要去那边
You shimmy. I'm gonna walk over here
看看有没有什么更好玩的事物
and find us a bigger, shinier something to do later.
还玩 不是准备回我们超舒服的公寓吗
Later? We're going home to our amazing apartment.
谁说的
Or not.
放松嘛 麦克斯 春假时间
Come on, Max, it's spring break.
就应该尽情享乐
Let's not get tied down.
我去那边看看
I'll be over there.
对 我们去那边看看
Yeah, we'll be over there.
抱歉 这里不允许带狗进来
Hi. You're not allowed to have dog in here.
除非小狗想买这本书
Unless he wants to buy the book.
你谁啊 美食保安吗
What are you, some kind of foodie bouncer?
更惨 我是这书的作者
Worse. I wrote the book.
你的手臂刺青不错
Yeah, nice sleeves.
09年刺青潮的时候刺的吗
You get those in the tattoo gold rush of '09?
我叫齐克 敢问芳姓大名
I'm Zeke. What's your name?
我叫麦克斯 这是我的小狗
I'm Max. This is my tiny dog.
老娘带着她到处跑 怎么着
I take her everywhere, so what?
麦克斯 想试试我的"厚片培根"吗
Hey, Max, you wanna try my thick-cut bacon?
再说吧 别猴急嘛
Maybe. Let's just take things slow.
相信我 那里有全世界最好吃的素炖菜
I'm telling you, it serves the best vegan stew anywhere.
强烈推荐你写上你的博客啊
You really should put it in your blog.
我再多写一篇有关素菜的博客
Oh, if I write one more article about something vegan,
我成千上万的粉丝就要手牵手
all of my devoted 10,000 readers will hold hands
一起跳楼自杀了
and jump collectively out a window.
我知道你喜欢发掘新鲜事物 引领新潮流
And I know you like to find what's new and what's next.
要吃巧克力培根吗
Chocolate bacon?
我过去跟人家谈一下
I just need a minute over there.
抱歉 不小心听到你们的谈话
Hi, couldn't help but overhear.
如果你想寻找美食界的新潮流
If you're looking for what's new,
我认识两个可爱的女孩
I found these two adorable girls
她们在威廉斯堡的家中
who run a cupcake business
有个自营的小蛋糕生意
out of their home in Williamsburg.
我知道听起来不靠谱 但她们真的是
I know how that sounds, but trust me,
未成名的新星 未经雕琢的璞玉
totally fresh and not at all overexposed.
你是什么身份 我为什么要听你...
And you're someone I should listen to because...?
抱歉 忘了自我介绍
Sorry, didn't introduce myself.
艾希莉·爱默生 《世界时装之苑》的时尚编辑
Ashley Emerson, style editor for Elle.
如果你有兴趣的话
If you're interested,
我包里好像有她们的名片
I think I might have a card in here somewhere.
本来是要留给玛莎的[美国家政女皇]
Was holding on to it for Martha.
培根先生人偶
Mr. Bacon action figure.
世界各地培根的试吃包
A world of bacon sampler.
抱歉里面还有一顶美食频道的潮帽
And I want to apologize for the food network trucker hat,
其实跟我这书半点关系都没有
which has nothing to do with bacon
完全是在突显我为五斗米折腰
and everything to do with me being a sellout.
你猜怎么着
Guess what.
艾希莉刚把我们的名片给了个女人
Ashley just gave our card to a woman
她拽得跟二五八万一样 肯定是号人物
who's such a bitch she must be important.
她是个美食博客写手
She's a food blogger.
虽然希望渺茫
It's a long shot,
但是我们真的需要打响招牌
but we need to get some exposure.
我们不是在放假吗
Whoa, we are on vacation.
说好了不谈公事的 还记得吗
No business talk. That was the deal, right?
他是齐克 厨师/作家/为五斗米折腰的男人
This is Zeke, chef-slash- author-slash-corporate sellout.
我们...
We were, uh...
我们刚想回公寓玩会儿呢
We were thinking about going back to the apartment to hang out.
感觉挺有意思啊
Oh, sounds fun.
我能单独跟你谈两句吗
Can I see you alone for a second?
没办法单独
Well, not alone.
老娘狗不离身 怎么着
I bring my tiny dog everywhere, so what?
我听他们说要去苏豪区办庆功宴
Come on, I heard of an after-party in Soho
再到登波区办庆功宴的庆功宴
and an after-after-party in dumbo.
咱们就去"舒好"吧
So, let's go-ho.
大玩特玩 让假期真正开始
Have fun and get this vacation started.
我抱着小狗在一个培根食谱的派对上
I'm holding a tiny dog at a bacon-book party
跟一个写培根书的男人有说有笑
and laughing with a guy who wrote a book about bacon.
我的假期早就开始了
I think my vacation's already started.
好吧 那你自己玩的开心点
All right, well, have fun.
我要去派对一番啦
I'm gonna go par-tay.
小艾艾 想干嘛就去吧
Eh, did your thing, Ash.
我不想说我炙手可热
I don't want to say that I'm hot.
但我兜里的"培根"已经熟了
But the bacon in my pocket is done.
说好五分钟一换的 你们俩混蛋
We said turns were five minutes, you bastards.
你们好 在享受桑拿吗
Oh, hi. More sauna fun.
麦克斯 能出来说句话吗
Max, can I see you in the hall for a second?
但该到我蒸蒸我这两球了呢
But it's my turn to sweat my balls off.
别以为我出去了 就不给你们计时了
Don't think the clock's not running while I'm out there.
我们能去度个真正的假期了
We're going on a real vacation.
你打包行李的速度能有多快
How quickly can you pack a bag?
不用担心没有合适的晚礼服
And don't worry about appropriate evening wear.
四季酒店的大厅里
Every Four Seasons has a Gucci
都有古琦跟宝格丽的专卖店
near the Bulgari store in the lobby.
完全听不懂那些字眼
None of those words made any sense.
你是不是春假中风发作了
I think you've had a spring break stroke.
我不是闹着玩的 楼下有车等着我们
No, seriously, there's a car waiting downstairs
要载我们去搭私人飞机呢
to take us to a private plane.
坐车到机场只需要20分钟
We can be at Teterboro in 20 minutes
然后飞8小时就能到大溪地了
and Tahiti in 8 hours.
一切费用 那个希腊人全包
The Greek is paying for everything.
他们喂你吃了什么药
What did they give you?
你能记得的最后一件事是什么
What's the last thing you can remember?
不是啦
Nothing.
我就喝了点水晶香槟
I just had some cristal.
是水晶冰毒吧
Some cristal meth?
不是啦 我只是挺兴奋的
No, I'm just really excited.
我在庆功宴上碰到这个船运大亨
I went to the after-party and this shipping magnate.
别担心 不是卖肉傍大款
Don't worry, it's not gonna be sexual.
而是干爹情
More like a father thing.
就跟我走嘛 能好好度假了
Anyway, let's go... finally got us a good vacation.
我们已经有个好假期了啊
But we're having a good vacation.
麦克斯 恕我直言
Max, don't take this personally,
但你根本不懂好假期的定义
but you don't know what a good vacation is
你一生坐井观天 犹如井底之蛙
because you've never been anywhere.
走进这间公寓时
I mean, you walked into that apartment
你都能眼神一亮 好像这是皇宫
and your face lit up, like... like it was amazing.
这单纯只是因为你见识的好东西太少了
And that's because you don't know that it's not.
相信我 我周游过列国
Trust me. I've been everywhere.
我很肯定的告诉你 这里的假期烂爆了
And I'm telling you, this is the worst vacation ever.
甩了培根怪胎跟酿酒兄吧
So let's ditch the bacon freak and the beer bro,
我们搭上飞机 去享受海滩一日游
get on that plane, spend one great day at the beach,
然后回来过一小时8块的生活
and then come back and make $8 an hour.
听起来不错
That sounds fun.
不过你少说了 我们被绑架后
You kind of skipped over the part where we get abducted
南希·格蕾丝的节目会花一年
and Nancy Grace covers the year-long search
来协寻我们的尸首
for our bodies.
应该是康斯坦丁打来了 他等的不耐烦了吧
It must be Constantine. He's gonna be upset.
希腊人最讨厌等待
You never keep a Greek waiting.
天啊 麦克斯 我们收到封邮件
Oh, my God, Max, we just got an email
是今天的美食博客写手发的
on our website from that food blogger at the book party.
她说明早给她送4个小蛋糕过去
She said if we drop off four cupcakes by tomorrow morning,
她就考虑在她的美食博客上美言几句
she'll consider writing about them for her column that day.
左右为难啊 要当卡洛琳还是艾希莉呢
Well, what's it gonna be, Caroline or Ashley?
小蛋糕还是大溪地 你挑吧
Cupcakes or Tahiti? Your call.
那个希腊人还在等吗
Is the Greek still waiting?
刚开走
He just pulled away.
有空他会回来找我的吧
I'm sure he'll come back here for Ashley sometime.
不过等他回来 我也不想当艾希莉
And when that happens, I wouldn't want to be her.
明天过后 你就被打回原形了
Well, after tomorrow, you won't be.
我能怎么办啊
What can I do?
你是问 当你的两种人格相遇
You mean after your two personalities
并自相残杀 该怎么办吗
meet and kill each other?
麦克斯 我说过我需要放个假
Max, I told you I needed a break.
只是没想到一放假 我就精神分裂
I just didn't know it was gonna be a psychotic one.
你真的要冷静一下了
You really need to chill.
你总是动不动就崩溃
You can't keep freaking out
就因为天不从人愿
because you're not where you want to be...
事不从你心
on vacation or in our business.
人生就是如此 别总是期望太高
I mean, it's life. Lower your expectations.
这个家酿啤酒还挺不错的呢
This microbrew is actually really good.
混入面粉中更美味
Tastes better in the batter.
帮我把那些枫蜜培根弄碎
Hey, crumble up some of that maple bacon for me.
说那些话真是对不起
Sorry about that stuff I said
我不是故意说你是井底之蛙的
about you never having gone anywhere.
干嘛道歉 我的确是井底之蛙
Why? I never have gone anywhere
坐井观天
or done anything.
我觉得我这样其实也不错
And now I'm thinking that's kind of a good thing,
至少我看见新事物还能兴奋
because I can still get excited and make a face
还能惊讶地合不拢嘴
when something's new to me.
因为对我来说 一切都是新事物
'Cause, basically, everything is.
这感觉一定很好吧
That must be nice.
来吧 试吃一下
All right, here, taste it.
混酒面粉加枫蜜培根的特制春假小蛋糕
My beer-batter, maple bacon, spring break cupcake.
天啊 你脸上有"新事物"的表情
Oh, my God, you made the "something new" face.
没错 因为是你创造了新事物
I did, because you made something new.
-太好吃了 -再做一次那表情
- It's delicious. - Do the face again.
回来啦 环游世界姐妹花
Oh, there they are, the world travelers.
大家怎么还不起身鼓掌撒花啊
Shouldn't people be throwing confetti or something?
我的花都用光了
I'm all out.
65年大停电的时候我当毒品吸掉了
I snorted mine in the power outage of '65.
假期玩得开心吗
How was your vacation?
虽然假期后来变成了一日游
Well, it turned out to be more of a daycation,
不过我们还是玩得很开心 对吧
but we had a great time, didn't we, Max?
是挺开心的
Yes, we did.
麦克斯 你走了之后餐厅了无生气啊
Max, things sure are dull around here without you.
周围的人嘴巴都干净得很
Everyone walking around all P.C.,
他娘的 都没人叫我黑鬼了
nobody called me black. Hell.
你走后我都没离开店过呢
I haven't left once since you've been gone.
工作上 你就是我的假期
When it comes to this job, you are my vacation.
就知道你这么好
And that, Earl, is why I got
所以给你带了五个礼物包
all five of these gift bags for you.
欢迎再次光临威廉斯堡餐厅
Welcome, again, to the Williamsburg diner.
这边请
This way, please.
我去维基百科查了"密柜中人"跟"米后"了
I have looked up "down-low" and "rice queen" on Wikipedia.
我不是未出柜的同性恋
And, no, I'm not a secret homosexual
对亚洲男人也没有特殊的基情
or a man who chases only Asian men.
我很好 我很"直" 接受现实吧
I'm great, I'm straight. Get used to it.
你们俩假期过得如何啊
Hi, guys. How was your vacation?
很好啊 你们在我们家玩的开心吗
Great. Did you have fun at our place?
当当然 你们家的桑拿爽歪了
Totes. Your saunas are sick.
我懂 基爆了对吧
I know. Could they be any gayer?
不是啦
No.
不过那天帮维诺娜清肛门腺后
Just one thing. Wynonna's still a little upset
她还一直心情低落呢
about the anal gland event.
什么
What?
我说了她不会懂我们是闹着玩的
I told you she wouldn't know it was a joke.
她怎么会不懂我们是闹着玩的呢
How could she not know it was a joke?
谁会叫别人去挤狗的肛门啊
I mean, who would ask someone to squeeze their dog's pooper?
我们再多付你50吧
We're paying you another 50.
兄弟 她插入你家小狗菊花的深度
Dude, she went second knuckle deep
有两个指节呢 你就多给50块而已啊
in your beagle's back door for only another 50?
谢了
Thank you.
还有件事
And just one other thing.
其实我们的生意挺惨淡的
Our business is actually not that great right now,
如果你们能帮忙介绍给朋友
so if you could recommend us to any of your friends,
-我们会感激不尽 -够诚实
- that would really help. - Good for you.
博客一宣传 生意就会蒸蒸日上了吧
I'm sure business will pick up after that blog blurb.
-什么博客宣传 -宣传你们的混酒面粉
- Wait, blog blurb? - About your beer-battered
加枫蜜培根特制春假小蛋糕啊
maple bacon spring break cupcake.
我们都在网上看到了
We just read about it.
是啊 就是那美食贱货的博客
Yeah, in that foodie bitch's blog.
麦克斯 成功了
Max, it worked.
快去用阿憨的电脑看看那篇博客吧
Let's go look at the blog on Han's computer.
失陪一下 我们马上回来
Excuse us. We'll be right back.
刚放完小假 立马有大突破啊
We got a little break and a big break.
是的 我又堕落了一次
Yeah, I did it again.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
你们错过了我人生中最美妙的两天
You missed the best two days of my life.